Ho-ho!
Look who's back reporting for duty.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hi.
Pam! Ha!
Look what I can do now that
she's no longer pregnant!
Bam! Bam! Bam! Pam!
Are you glad
to be back?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I could have
used another week, or three.
You still had eight
weeks more than we did.
Well, it's not
exactly a vacation.
Hello, everyone! Remember?
Little old me. Hi.
What are you doing here?
You just had our baby.
Our collective Dunder Mifflin
family baby four days ago.
I wanted to come
back to work.
Not everybody needs some long,
luxurious, Parisian maternity leave.
Damn, girl! Your body!
What?
Angela, you
look amazing.
Really? I feel like
this big rhinoceros.
Anyway, I wanted to thank you guys for
covering for me, so I made some treats.
I've got brownies
and magic cookie bars.
Mm-mm-mm.
Angela, those brownies have walnuts in them
and I think Kevin's allergic to walnuts.
You're allergic to
walnuts, right, Kevin?
Extremely, but I'm going
to fight through it.
It's okay, Angela.
I have mommy brain, too.
I don't know
what that is, Pam.
I made a batch with no nuts, special
for you, Kevin. Right here.
When did you find time
to do all this?
Babies sleep a lot, Pam,
if you feed them enough.
Brownie, Pam?
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
It's really good.
I wouldn't know.
I'm watching my weight.
Say, guys, you know what's an even
more useful treat is cash. So...
Nope. It's over. No. Okay. We
wanted to say thank you...
Dwight, I have exciting
news for you. What?
I think you're
going to like it.
You can't tantalize me.
Oh, maybe I can.
I got an e-mail
from corporate
that told me...
Okay.
...that you got
a promotion!
Right? I mean, that's not the kind of thing
you want to read quietly at your desk.
If you make me head of sales
one more time, I swear.
No. This is legit.
You will be assembling a team to
go to Tallahassee for three weeks
to develop and launch
a chain of Sabre stores.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
The Schrutes
have a word for when
everything in a man's life
comes together perfectly.
"Perfektenschlag."
Right now, I'm in it.
I finally get a chance to
prove myself to corporate.
I am assembling a competent team.
I am likely a father.
I am so deep inside of
perfektenschlag right now.
And just to be clear,
there is a second definition,
"perfect pork anus,"
which I don't mean.
And here's
the fax for you.
some facts for you.
Did you know frogs can
hear with their lungs?
And that flamingos can have
orgasms that last 30 minutes.
Love to learn. Yeah, it's weird
that I said that last one.
So...
Yeah, look at that.
We're pin twins.
Pin twins.
This is a gift from Jessica.
Kind of a gag gift, really.
Real gifts come later.
Yeah. That's cute.
When I saw it at CVS,
it made me gag, too. Just...
For a while there, I thought
something would change,but nope.
Andy's still with Jessica.
They even carpool
together most days.
I don't know.
I wouldn't mind carpooling
every day with Andy,
but I wouldn't want to spend
that much time with Jessica.
What do we have here?
Val knit me a beanie.
But I can't tell if it's a
"We're just friends" beanie,
or a "I'm hot, you're hot,
let's get it popping" beanie.
So I'm going
to up the ante.
Give her a clearly
romantic gift.
And we'll get to the
meaning of the beanie.
Pam, pack up your
post-natal swimwear,
make it a one piece or
this offer is rescinded,
and join me for a fantastic barbeque one
week from today in Tallahassee, Florida,
where I'm going to be living
for the next three weeks.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I'll fly anywhere
for some good barbeque.
Ooh, me three.
No plus ones.
This is for competent workers only.
And don't worry about the cost.
Sabre is footing the bill.
Does this have anything to do with
what you were talking to Andy about?
God, you're
such a spy.
Notice anything
different about me?
You're wearing the beanie.
You like it?
Super comfortable. Like
sweatpants for my head.
I love it too, Val.
It's really itchy,
uh, but to be fair, my head
is constantly itching,
so I can't really
peg it on the hat.
Wow. It's like the Nation
of Islam down here.
I like to knit,
don't hate.
Who's that for?
Oh. This is a gift for
my man Nate here.
What?
Yeah.
Darryl, you
shouldn't have.
Can I open it? No,no,no,
maybe just later.
Ah, I can't wait. I'm sorry.
I'm too excited.
Darryl.
Wow. Those
are really nice.
They're so elegant.
Cashmere.
How did you know?
Just a hunch.
Your gift is on the way.
Can't wait.
"I'm glad you're in my life.
Happy Valentine's Day."
Darryl, I am glad
to be in your life, too.
Your card is more
beautiful than the gloves.
My first task as special
project manager Dwight Schrute,
assembling a crack team.
I need people who are loyal,
people who will help me get an inroad
with the gay Hispanic community.
People who won't be missed.
We don't need idiots.
Good for nothings.
Meth heads.
Or...
What's your name?
Cathy.
I just got a text from
Robert California that says,
"Bring your clubs
to Florida."
Why? Does he think you're
going to Florida?
I hope not. Because
I am not going.
Two question marks?
No, just do one. Two question
marks is kind of aggressive.
You know, it's like,
"Well, what?"
Just do one.
You want to take Darryl,
Phyllis, Toby, Angela and Oscar?
Yes.
Can I interest you
in someone less essential?
Like a Creed or a
Meredith, perhaps?
Oh, my God. They're not
expendable exactly.
I just can't... I can't think
of the word I'm trying to find.
Are you kidding me?
I'm supposed to get on an
airplane with those nincompoops?
We'd never make it
off the runway!
All right, look, I got to keep
this office functioning somehow,
so I have put
together a list.
Here's your team.
Darryl and Phyllis,
you can have.
You're also taking Cathy,
Kelly and Kevin.
Oh, God.
You have your team.
Kevin? Kelly? Cathy?
Andy just gave me a chain
with three weak links.
Have you ever tried to use a chain
with three weak links? I have.
And now I no longer
own an Arctic Wolf.
Well, let's hear it.
"Robert, hey," exclamation point.
I like it so far.
"Got your text.
Awesome idea.
"Let's hit the links the next
time you're in PA. -J.H."
It's perfect. You emphasize the
golf, completely omit the Florida.
Yeah, it's a golf text.
Total golf text. Send it.
Done. Wait, I just feel weird.
I should just call him.
You want to call someone that texted you?
Do you want to drive them away? I mean...
This is Darryl.
Sorry, I asked for
the main shipment number.
I just need the address
for the warehouse.
I want to send my
girlfriend some flowers.
Your girlfriend?
ls your girlfriend Val?
Yeah. Do you know her?
We're friends.
Cool. So can I get
that address or...
Yeah, yeah. Sorry, I'm
just looking for a pen.
Why do you
need a pen?
Back off.
I got my reasons.
May I have your
attention, please?
Could Cathy, Phyllis,
Darryl, Kevin and Kelly
please join me in the
conference room immediately?
Why?
No big deal.
It's just that you five have been
deemed most deserving of a three-week,
all expenses paid business
trip to Tallahassee, Florida.
Hell, yeah.
What?
I'm sorry, Stanley. I can't share
any more details with you.
You see,
Andy rejected you.
Wait,
Cathy gets to go?
Why does she even still work here?
Pam is back.
It just feels like
a slap in the face.
I can understand your pain.
And your rage.
But you know what?
Andy is an honorable man.
Let us not question his choices.
I'm sure he had his reasons.
We're not questioning his reasons.
I just want to know what they are.
I know. You and me
both, brother.
It seemed kind
of random to me,
but he was pretty clear on who he thought
truly deserved this boondoggle of a lifetime.
Well, he nailed it, because
I do deserve a vacation.
Sometimes Batman's
got to take off his cape.
Good point. But we're going to be
working pretty hard until 5:00 p.m.
After that, it's going to be beach
volleyball, trips to Cape Canaveral
and sea kayaking
with Gloria Estefan.
What were the
criteria for going?
It might be innate goodness
versus innate badness.
But there's an easy
way to find out.
Oh, Andy, got a few
questions for you.
Moshi moshi
Uh, the Florida
picks got out,
and people were just kind of curious
as to why they weren't picked,
and maybe you
could just clarify.
Uh...
Well, the deliberations were confidential,
so I feel like we should respect that.
Respect it? You're
trying to tell me
Kevin Malone deserves more
than Stanley Hudson?
Hey.
Okay, it's obvious
that Andy picked the people that
are least important to the office.
Important? Because you and
your enormous monster baby
are so important
to the branch?
My baby is
not a monster.
Hey, be proud of your
enormous monster baby.
I was once an enormous
monster baby.
Guys! Guys! Guys!
Come on, seriously, we cannot let this
trip cause this kind of rift, guys.
Stop calling us "guys"!
I use the word "guys" a lot
when I'm nervous, guys.
- Guys, guys, guys. Guys.
- Stop it.
Stop! Stop it! Andy.
Dudes.
The dudes who are going to Florida
were picked by Dwight and me.
Okay, hey, I
specifically remember
that there were a lot of other people
I thought should be considered.
Uh...
If anybody's going to
Florida, it should be me.
Every shirt that I have that isn't
a work shirt is a Tommy Bahama.
I'm the only person in this
office who watches Burn Notice.
Okay. I did not realize that so
many of you wanted to go so badly,
so if you feel like you have a
very good reason to go to Florida,
I'm happy to hear you out.
Great idea.
So why doesn't everyone just
take the next five to six hours,
come up with a statement on why you
feel you deserve to go to Florida,
and Andy and I
will listen to it.
No, that is a ridiculous waste of time.
For you maybe.
Five to six hours?
Three to four hours.
No,no,no,no.No.
Just two to three hours.
Come up with a statement
over the next hour.
Thirty minutes.
I'm out.
Okay, read it
back to me.
"Robert, great offer. Wish I could
hit the links with you in Florida,
"but a father of a newborn really should be
helping out his wife any chance he gets."
Good. Doesn't sound pushy.
You're just stating a fact.
Absolutely.
Works for me.
Okay. Sending.
Well done. And we managed
to kill the entire morning.
We really did.
He responded, "L.O.L."
I have a new swimsuit I need to break in.
I am already...
I already picked my team, Darryl,
Oscar, Angela, Phyllis and Toby.
And that is the team
that I am taking.
What's that? It's not up to me?
I only have influence?
Well, that's all
Baltzer Glattfuelder had,
and now no one eats
owls for Thanksgiving.
You have two young, dynamic
people in this office
who know trends,
who know youth.
That's myself and Kelly Kapoor,
you need one of us there.
Or both? Not both. Just one. Me.
Or if not me, Kelly.
Ideally me.
Again, youth knowledge,
that's what you get when you put Ryan
Howard on your special project team.
Or Kelly Kapoor.
Again, not both. Thanks.
Very impressive.
He put a lot of work into that.
Mm-hmm.
PowerPoints are the peacocks
of the business world.
All show, no meat.
Because I feel like that I am in
a place with my gambling rehab
that I can finally start
going to dog racing again.
You know, just sitting,
watching, enjoying the sport.
Maybe putting down a few dollars if there's
like a crazy mismatch or something.
Okay. Thank you, Kevin,
we'll let you know.
Thank you.
When do we leave?
It really has been
a long, lonely winter.
Wow. Seasonal affective
disorder, a.k.a. SAD.
That sounds like
a very real thing, Toby.
It is real. Thank you
for saying that.
Yeah, wow,
it's almost like
we're not all experiencing
the same winter.
Florida Stanley smiles. Florida
Stanley is happy to go to work.
Florida Stanley is who you
want on your Florida team.
It's still... Well.
...she does here.
Hey, guys.
Any spots left?
Erin, you want to go
to Tallahassee?
I do. I really do.
I think it would be a nice
way to clear my head.
You know, I don't think it's a good
idea for you to clear your head
any more than it
has been already.
I think you need
a workplace where
the burdens of everyday life
keep you tethered to reality.
Either or.
But if you can find someone to
fill in, I would love to go.
Well, it wouldn't be hard
to find someone to fill in.
Really? Oh, great. Good.
Now, is it too dark to say that
Cece's having an operation?
I think you need
to go to Florida.
I think you're right.
It's only for three weeks.
You know, with my mom and sister
at the house, it'll be...
A total nightmare.
I was going to say good, because
I'll have all the help I need.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
They're incredibly helpful.
You're lucky
to have them.
With them there, you probably
won't even know I'm gone.
Exactly.
Well...
No. No! Absolutely not. You are not going!
Over my dead body, no. Andy...
Toons, I'm really sorry.
You're too essential to the operation here.
I can't let you go.
I wouldn't say that.
That's a bit much.
You know, Dwight, if you
didn't want me to go,
the smart move would be to tell Andy that
I actually am essential to the operation.
That way, I couldn't go.
Jim is essential... Hold on. I
just want to get it on camera.
Andy, Jim is just too...
Essential
This is stupid! Cut!
All right. I'm going
to pack my trunks.
He doesn't even
want to go.
Well, I got a text
from R.C.
inviting me to come down, so I think
that's going to make us roommates.
Oh, my God.
Hey, quick question, do you shower at night?
Or do you shower in the morning?
Because I want to shower when you're
showering to save some water.
Okay, listen up, everyone.
Here's who's going to Florida.
Cathy.
What?
Stanley.
No.
Ryan.
No!
Erin.
And Jim.
You got to be
kidding me. Okay.
Okay.
Florida group,
welcome to the team.
Let's go!
Step it up, you runts.
You infants. Let's move.
Why is it so
hot in here?
Hot? What are you talking about? This
is a nice, temperate Florida morning.
Eighty-five degrees,
73% humidity.
This is the exact environment
that you will be facing
for the next three
weeks of your life.
Welcome to Special
Projects orientation.
The next three weeks
of your life
are going to be the most
miserable you've ever faced.
They're going to be hard.
They're going to be dirty.
You're going to
wish you were dead.
But?
"But?" There's no "buts."
That's it. You'll wish you were dead.
You seem a little disturbed.
Do you want to stay here?
No. No. I want to go.
Because if any of you
would prefer to stay here,
all you need to do
is ring this bell.
Is that the buzzer
from Taboo?
Shut up, maggot!
It is.
You don't want to go,
ring the bell!
Ring it. Ring it.
How many of you have seen the
documentary Deliverance?
How did a mosquito
get in here?
I released 300 mosquitoes
into the conference room.
Just temporarily.
When I'm done, the frogs will
take care of the mosquitoes.
Yes. And then he brushes
your soft supple cheeks
with his worn leathery
hands and says,
"I'm going to make you
the seventh Mrs. Rosenblat!"
Unless you ring
the bell. Ring it.
No.
Ring the bell.
You want to spend the rest of your life
changing your husband's colostomy bags?
Huh? Do you? Ring it!
What? Ah.
What was that?
Mosquito.
Orientation's over.
Darryl, hey.
Hey, what's up?
You called?
Yeah, you know,
I felt really terrible
that you got me these lovely gloves,
and I didn't get you anything.
It's cool, really.
No, it's anything
but cool
Now, I haven't really had time to
go out and buy you anything, but
here goes.
"This coupon entitles you to one
free tickle monster attack."
Yeah. They're Nate coupons or Nate-pons.
And they're all different.
Cash that one in and I will
bring you a stick of gum
any time, any place.
I'll find you.
Thanks.
Nice flowers.
Thanks.They're
from my mom.
Your mom?
Yeah.
Oh.
So I guess that was your mom who called
me earlier looking for the address.
Real deep-voiced woman.
Yeah, that's her.
She said her name
was Brandon, I think.
Your mom's name
is Brandon?
Yeah, Darryl. My mom's
name is Brandon.
I guess I figured
out where I stand.
This is a love beanie.
Okay, Florida team,
let's reconvene.
I'm going to Florida.
And I'm not coming back.
So Sabre has set up a conference room
for our use while we're at corporate.
So what is this
special project?
Basically, Sabre has
tasked us with
helping them branch into
the retail market place.
They want to set up their own
version of an Apple store.
That sounds awesome.
It did. It did.
You know what
might be great?
Is if instead of a genius
bar, we have a lounge area
where people can ask
questions about the product
with other customers
who liked it.
Yeah, and they should have a place where
people can check their computers or printers
before they see you, so you don't
have to carry it around like a dope.
Like a coat check.
Oh, don't write it down
unless you like it.
Oh, I like it.
It seems to me that the Apple
store is kind of like a party,
so I think our question is, how
do we make this a better party?
No. We sell business tools and
the stores need to reflect that.
They need to be all business. Let all
the other stores look like a toy store.
Right. Think different.
From Apple.
Dwight, is now a good time to
go over what you expect of us?
Yes.
What are my expectations
for the group?
I have been given the responsibility
to manage Stanley, a solid player.
Ryan, who is capable
of surprises.
Erin, an excellent
follower.
And Cathy, a probably not
totally useless enigma.
And, well, Jim.
Under the right manager,
that's not a bad team.
Perfektenschlag.
I don't know how I'm going
to live here without you.
Me neither. Hey, will you
put this coat on my chair?
I just realized I'm not going
to need it down there.
Yes, I will take
your coat.
And I will keep it
with me,
and I will sleep with it
because it smells like you.
No,no,no,no,no.
Just put it on my chair.
All right.
Bye.
Bye. Call me when you land.
I will.
Safe travels!
Goodbye for a very,
very long time.
Okay.
It's only three weeks.
All expenses paid.
Yeah. Jim's going
to be there.
That marriage is not good.
Nobody knows better than me.
Definitely, we will.
It's three weeks in Tallahassee.
What else is there to do?